export default {
  id: 'mid_6b',
  name: '상용한자(중학6/한자찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: '독:たて/음:じゅん', answer: ['盾'] },
    { question: '독:돌/음:じゅん', answer: ['循'] },
    { question: '독:いも/음:', answer: ['芋'] },
    { question: '독:겨룰/음:こう', answer: ['抗'] },
    { question: '독:구덩이/음:こう', answer: ['坑'] },
    { question: '독:はだ/음:', answer: ['肌'] },
    { question: '독:う(える)/음:き', answer: ['飢'] },
    { question: '독:쓸데없을/음:じょう', answer: ['冗'] },
    { question: '독:なまり/음:えん', answer: ['鉛'] },
    { question: '독:작을/음:び', answer: ['微'] },
    { question: '독:부를/음:ちょう', answer: ['徴'] },
    { question: '독:こ(りる)、こ(らす)、こ(らしめる)/음:ちょう', answer: ['懲'] },
    { question: '독:무릇/음:ぼん、[はん]', answer: ['凡'] },
    { question: '독:ほ/음:はん', answer: ['帆'] },
    { question: '독:뜰, 넓을/음:はん', answer: ['汎'] },
    { question: '독:おそ(れる)、おそ(ろしい)/음:きょう', answer: ['恐'] },
    { question: '독:あらし/음:', answer: ['嵐'] },
    { question: '독:넘칠/음:はん', answer: ['氾'] },
    { question: '독:법/음:はん', answer: ['範'] },
    { question: '독:재앙/음:やく', answer: ['厄'] },
    { question: '독:원망할, 쌓을/음:えん、おん', answer: ['怨'] },
    { question: '독:あ(てる)/음:', answer: ['宛'] },
    { question: '독:うで/음:わん', answer: ['腕'] },
    { question: '독:おろ(す)、おろし/음:', answer: ['卸'] },
    { question: '독:おん/음:きょ、ご', answer: ['御'] },
    { question: '독:すず/음:れい、りん', answer: ['鈴'] },
    { question: '독:떨어질, 영(0)/음:れい', answer: ['零'] },
    { question: '독:나이/음:れい', answer: ['齢'] },
    { question: '독:やなぎ/음:りゅう', answer: ['柳'] },
    { question: '독:あお(ぐ)、おお(せ)/음:ぎょう、[こう]', answer: ['仰'] },
    { question: '독:おさ(える)/음:よく', answer: ['抑'] },
    { question: '독:むか(える)/음:げい', answer: ['迎'] },
    { question: '독:유리/음:る', answer: ['瑠'] },
    { question: '독:か(ける)、か(る)/음:く', answer: ['駆'] },
    { question: '독:구라파/음:おう', answer: ['欧'] },
    { question: '독:なぐ(る)/음:おう', answer: ['殴'] },
    { question: '독:지도리, 축/음:すう', answer: ['枢'] },
    { question: '독:く(る)/음:', answer: ['繰'] },
    { question: '독:마를/음:そう', answer: ['燥'] },
    { question: '독:も/음:そう', answer: ['藻'] },
    { question: '독:おか/음:', answer: ['岡'] },
    { question: '독:굳셀/음:ごう', answer: ['剛'] },
    { question: '독:つな/음:こう', answer: ['綱'] },
    { question: '독:큰창자, 몸통/음:どう', answer: ['胴'] },
    { question: '독:ほら/음:どう', answer: ['洞'] },
    { question: '독:つつ/음:とう', answer: ['筒'] },
    { question: '독:울타리/음:さく', answer: ['柵'] },
    { question: '독:윤리/음:りん', answer: ['倫'] },
    { question: '독:かたよ(る)/음:へん', answer: ['偏'] },
    { question: '독:두루/음:へん', answer: ['遍'] },
    { question: '독:돈, 폐백/음:へい', answer: ['幣'] },
    { question: '독:폐단/음:へい', answer: ['弊'] },
    { question: '독:덮을/음:へい', answer: ['蔽'] },
    { question: '독:えら(い)/음:い', answer: ['偉'] },
    { question: '독:씨실/음:い', answer: ['緯'] },
    { question: '독:ちが(う)、ちが(える)/음:い', answer: ['違'] },
    { question: '독:かわ(く)、かわ(かす)/음:かん', answer: ['乾'] },
    { question: '독:한국/음:かん', answer: ['韓'] },
    { question: '독:あざけ(る)/음:ちょう', answer: ['嘲'] },
    { question: '독:뛰어날/음:けつ', answer: ['傑'] },
    { question: '독:またた(く)/음:しゅん', answer: ['瞬'] },
    { question: '독:とな(る)、となり/음:りん', answer: ['隣'] },
    { question: '독:ま(う)、まい/음:ぶ', answer: ['舞'] },
    { question: '독:곧을/음:そく', answer: ['即'] },
    { question: '독:すで(に)/음:き', answer: ['既'] },
    { question: '독:슬퍼할/음:がい', answer: ['慨'] },
    { question: '독:대개/음:がい', answer: ['概'] },
    { question: '독:복/음:し', answer: ['祉'] },
    { question: '독:즐길/음:こう', answer: ['肯'] },
    { question: '독:くわだ(てる)/음:き', answer: ['企'] },
    { question: '독:しぶ、しぶ(い)、しぶ(る)/음:じゅう', answer: ['渋'] },
    { question: '독:め、めす/음:し', answer: ['雌'] },
    { question: '독:むらさき/음:し', answer: ['紫'] },
    { question: '독:진척될/음:ちょく', answer: ['捗'] },
    { question: '독:건널/음:しょう', answer: ['渉'] },
    { question: '독:자주/음:ひん', answer: ['頻'] },
    { question: '독:칠/음:せい', answer: ['征'] },
    { question: '독:병세/음:しょう', answer: ['症'] },
    { question: '독:덩어리/음:じょう', answer: ['錠'] },
    { question: '독:ほころびる/음:たん', answer: ['綻'] },
    { question: '독:옳을, 이/음:ぜ', answer: ['是'] },
    { question: '독:つつみ/음:てい', answer: ['堤'] },
    { question: '독:うなが(す)/음:そく', answer: ['促'] },
    { question: '독:とら(える)/음:そく', answer: ['捉'] },
    { question: '독:むこ/음:せい', answer: ['婿'] },
    { question: '독:돌/음:せん', answer: ['旋'] },
    { question: '독:비길, 흉내낼/음:ぎ', answer: ['擬'] },
    { question: '독:こ(る)、こ(らす)/음:ぎょう', answer: ['凝'] },
    { question: '독:いしずえ/음:そ', answer: ['礎'] },
    { question: '독:신선/음:せん', answer: ['仙'] },
    { question: '독:とうげ/음:', answer: ['峠'] },
    { question: '독:つたな(い)/음:せつ', answer: ['拙'] },
    { question: '독:굽힐/음:くつ', answer: ['屈'] },
    { question: '독:ほり/음:', answer: ['堀'] },
    { question: '독:ほ(る)/음:くつ', answer: ['掘'] },
    { question: '독:구멍굴/음:くつ', answer: ['窟'] },
    { question: '독:つぼ/음:', answer: ['坪'] },
    { question: '독:まぎ(れる)、まぎ(らす)、まぎ(らわす)、まぎ(らわしい)/음:ふん', answer: ['紛'] },
    { question: '독:동이/음:ぼん', answer: ['盆'] },
    { question: '독:눈날릴/음:ふん', answer: ['雰'] }
  ]
}
